* Toggle Sub Menu [Projects](#)
* Toggle Sub Menu [Resources](#)

Privacy Policy
==============

Effective May 20th, 2024

Welcome to [oldgate.org](https://oldgate.org/) (the “Site”). We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site. This statement governs our privacy policies concerning those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by Oldgate Studios (collectively, “Services”) (“Authorized Customers”).

Personally Identifiable Information
-----------------------------------

“Personally Identifiable Information” refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?
------------------------------------------------------

We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors.

How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?
----------------------------------------------------------

We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site and to fulfill requests made by Visitors. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors in response to specific inquiries or to provide requested information.

With whom may the information be shared?
----------------------------------------

We do not sell or share Personally Identifiable Information with any third parties, including government or authorities.

How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?
--------------------------------------------------

Personally Identifiable Information collected by Oldgate Studios is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or members of Oldgate Studios except for use as indicated above.

What choices are available to Visitors regarding the collection, use, and distribution of the information?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Visitors may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from us by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://oldgate.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Cookies
-------

We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

What partners or service providers can access Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site?
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We do not have partners or service providers that access Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site.

How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Visitors may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://oldgate.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Can a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site?
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Visitors may request the deletion or deactivation of Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site by contacting us. However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor’s entry without retaining some residual information.

Your rights
-----------

These are summarized rights that you have under the data protection law:

* The right to access
* The right to rectification
* The right to erasure
* The right to restrict processing
* The right to object to processing
* The right to data portability
* The right to complain to a supervisory authority
* The right to withdraw consent

Children’s Privacy
------------------

Our Service does not address “Children”, anyone under the age of 18 years of age, and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18 years old.

What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?
-------------------------------------------

We will let our Visitors know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site.

Collection of Data
------------------

In order to enhance user experience and provide tailored content, we collect country data from Visitors accessing the Site. This information helps us deliver localized content and services to better serve the needs of our users. Additionally, we collect anonymized IP addresses (with the last octet removed) to assist in the moderation of our site’s content. This data is used solely for moderation purposes and does not include personally identifiable information unless voluntarily provided by the user. We are committed to safeguarding this data in accordance with our privacy policy.

Security Measures for User-Identifiable Data
--------------------------------------------

Passwords and other user-identifiable data are stored in databases encrypted using Elliptic Curve Cryptography (ECC) or Diffie-Hellman encryption methods. These robust encryption techniques ensure the security and confidentiality of sensitive user information. We are committed to maintaining the integrity of user data and employ advanced encryption protocols to safeguard it from unauthorized access or breaches.

Links
-----

[oldgate.org](https://oldgate.org/) contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another website. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://oldgate.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Oldgate Studios. Built In Oregon & Australia with 💜
